<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Das Kopfkino</title>
        <description>Still alive. With luck. No worry. Thanks.</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:44:34 +0100</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:44:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.0.1</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>친구 그리고 아는 사람</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;썸네일 보여지는 문장이다. 대통령은 내우·외환·천재·지변 또는 중대한 재정·경제상의 위기에 있어서 국가의 안전보장 또는 공공의 안녕질서를 유지하기 위하여 긴급한 조치가 필요하고 국회의 집회를 기다릴 여유가 없을 때에 한하여 최소한으로 필요한 재정·경제상의 처분을 하거나 이에 관하여 법률의 효력을 가지는 명령을 발할 수 있다. 의무교육은 무상으로 한다. 헌법개정안은 국회가 의결한 후 30일 이내에 국민투표에 붙여 국회의원선거권자 과반수의 투표와 투표자 과반수의 찬성을 얻어야 한다. 대통령은 헌법과 법률이 정하는 바에 의하여 국군을 통수한다. 국군은 국가의 안전보장과 국토방위의 신성한 의무를 수행함을 사명으로 하며, 그 정치적 중립성은 준수된다.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
두번째 문단이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;세번째 문단이다.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC-%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0-%EC%95%84%EB%8A%94-%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC-%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0-%EC%95%84%EB%8A%94-%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C</guid>
                
                <category>life</category>
                
                <category>thoughts</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Graphic Designer On The Road</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer is a professional within the graphic design and graphic arts industry who assembles together images, typography, or motion graphics to create a piece of design. A graphic designer creates the graphics primarily for published, printed or electronic media, such as brochures (sometimes) and advertising. They are also sometimes responsible for typesetting, illustration, user interfaces, web design, or take a teaching position. A core responsibility of the designer’s job is to present information in a way that is both accessible and memorable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A degree or certificate from an accredited trade school is usually considered essential for a graphic design position. After a career history has been established, though, the graphic designer’s experience and number of years in the business are considered the primary qualifications. A portfolio, which is the primary method for demonstrating these qualifications, is usually required to be shown at job interviews, and is constantly developed throughout a designer’s career. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Graphic_designer&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ice molecules can exhibit up to sixteen different phases &lt;em&gt;(packing geometries)&lt;/em&gt; that depend on temperature and pressure. When water is cooled rapidly (quenching), up to three different types of amorphous ice can form depending on the history of its pressure and temperature. When cooled slowly correlated proton tunneling occurs below 20 K giving rise to macroscopic quantum phenomena. Virtually all the ice on Earth’s surface and in its atmosphere is of a hexagonal crystalline structure denoted as ice Ih (spoken as “ice one h”) with minute traces of cubic ice denoted as ice Ic. The most common phase transition to ice Ih occurs when liquid water is cooled below 0°C (273.15K, 32°F) at standard atmospheric pressure. It may also be deposited directly by water vapor, as happens in the formation of frost. The transition from ice to water is melting and from ice directly to water vapor is sublimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;characteristics&quot;&gt;Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a naturally-occurring crystalline inorganic solid with an ordered structure, ice is considered a mineral.[citation needed] It possesses a regular crystalline structure based on the molecule of water, which consists of a single oxygen atom covalently bonded to two hydrogen atoms, or H-O-H. However, many of the physical properties of water and ice are controlled by the formation of hydrogen bonds between adjacent oxygen and hydrogen atoms; while it is a weak bond, it is nonetheless critical in controlling the structure of both water and ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ice contains no future , just the past, sealed away. As if they’re alive, everything in the world is sealed up inside, clear and distinct. Ice can preserve all kinds of things that way- cleanly, clearly. That’s the essence of ice, the role it plays.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Haruki Murakami&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unusual property of ice frozen at atmospheric pressure is that the solid is approximately 8.3% less dense than liquid water. The density of ice is 0.9167 g/cm3 at 0 °C,[4] whereas water has a density of 0.9998 g/cm³ at the same temperature. Liquid water is densest, essentially 1.00 g/cm³, at 4 °C and becomes less dense as the water molecules begin to form the hexagonal crystals[5] of ice as the freezing point is reached. This is due to hydrogen bonding dominating the intermolecular forces, which results in a packing of molecules less compact in the solid. Density of ice increases slightly with decreasing temperature and has a value of 0.9340 g/cm³ at −180 °C (93 K).[6]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When water freezes, it increases in volume (about 9% for freshwater).[7] The effect of expansion during freezing can be dramatic, and ice expansion is a basic cause of freeze-thaw weathering of rock in nature and damage to building foundations and roadways from frost heaving. It is also a common cause of the flooding of houses when water pipes burst due to the pressure of expanding water when it freezes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of this process is that ice &lt;em&gt;(in its most common form)&lt;/em&gt; floats on liquid water, which is an important feature in Earth’s biosphere. It has been argued that without this property, natural bodies of water would freeze, in some cases permanently, from the bottom up,[8] resulting in a loss of bottom-dependent animal and plant life in fresh and sea water. Sufficiently thin ice sheets allow light to pass through while protecting the underside from short-term weather extremes such as wind chill. This creates a sheltered environment for bacterial and algal colonies. When sea water freezes, the ice is riddled with brine-filled channels which sustain sympagic organisms such as bacteria, algae, copepods and annelids, which in turn provide food for animals such as krill and specialised fish like the bald notothen, fed upon in turn by larger animals such as emperor penguins and minke whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ice melts, it absorbs as much energy as it would take to heat an equivalent mass of water by 80 °C. During the melting process, the temperature remains constant at 0 °C. While melting, any energy added breaks the hydrogen bonds between ice (water) molecules. Energy becomes available to increase the thermal energy (temperature) only after enough hydrogen bonds are broken that the ice can be considered liquid water. The amount of energy consumed in breaking hydrogen bonds in the transition from ice to water is known as the heat of fusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with water, ice absorbs light at the red end of the spectrum preferentially as the result of an overtone of an oxygen-hydrogen (O-H) bond stretch. Compared with water, this absorption is shifted toward slightly lower energies. Thus, ice appears blue, with a slightly greener tint than for liquid water. Since absorption is cumulative, the color effect intensifies with increasing thickness or if internal reflections cause the light to take a longer path through the ice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>예술가의 피</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;썸네일 보여지는 문장이다. 대통령은 내우·외환·천재·지변 또는 중대한 재정·경제상의 위기에 있어서 국가의 안전보장 또는 공공의 안녕질서를 유지하기 위하여 긴급한 조치가 필요하고 국회의 집회를 기다릴 여유가 없을 때에 한하여 최소한으로 필요한 재정·경제상의 처분을 하거나 이에 관하여 법률의 효력을 가지는 명령을 발할 수 있다. 의무교육은 무상으로 한다. 헌법개정안은 국회가 의결한 후 30일 이내에 국민투표에 붙여 국회의원선거권자 과반수의 투표와 투표자 과반수의 찬성을 얻어야 한다. 대통령은 헌법과 법률이 정하는 바에 의하여 국군을 통수한다. 국군은 국가의 안전보장과 국토방위의 신성한 의무를 수행함을 사명으로 하며, 그 정치적 중립성은 준수된다.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;사법권은 법관으로 구성된 법원에 속한다. 대통령은 국회에 출석하여 발언하거나 서한으로 의견을 표시할 수 있다. 국무회의는 정부의 권한에 속하는 중요한 정책을 심의한다. 국회에 제출된 법률안 기타의 의안은 회기중에 의결되지 못한 이유로 폐기되지 아니한다. 다만, 국회의원의 임기가 만료된 때에는 그러하지 아니하다. 선거에 관한 경비는 법률이 정하는 경우를 제외하고는 정당 또는 후보자에게 부담시킬 수 없다. 이 헌법시행 당시의 법령과 조약은 이 헌법에 위배되지 아니하는 한 그 효력을 지속한다. 국회는 정부의 동의없이 정부가 제출한 지출예산 각항의 금액을 증가하거나 새 비목을 설치할 수 없다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;감사원은 원장을 포함한 5인 이상 11인 이하의 감사위원으로 구성한다. 계엄을 선포한 때에는 대통령은 지체없이 국회에 통고하여야 한다. 국민경제자문회의의 조직·직무범위 기타 필요한 사항은 법률로 정한다. 민주평화통일자문회의의 조직·직무범위 기타 필요한 사항은 법률로 정한다. 대통령후보자가 1인일 때에는 그 득표수가 선거권자 총수의 3분의 1 이상이 아니면 대통령으로 당선될 수 없다. 대통령의 임기연장 또는 중임변경을 위한 헌법개정은 그 헌법개정 제안 당시의 대통령에 대하여는 효력이 없다. 모든 국민은 양심의 자유를 가진다. 대통령이 제1항의 기간내에 공포나 재의의 요구를 하지 아니한 때에도 그 법률안은 법률로서 확정된다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;모든 국민은 언론·출판의 자유와 집회·결사의 자유를 가진다. 대통령의 임기는 5년으로 하며, 중임할 수 없다. 모든 국민은 종교의 자유를 가진다. 국가는 지역간의 균형있는 발전을 위하여 지역경제를 육성할 의무를 진다. 헌법개정안이 제2항의 찬성을 얻은 때에는 헌법개정은 확정되며, 대통령은 즉시 이를 공포하여야 한다. 대통령·국무총리·국무위원·행정각부의 장·헌법재판소 재판관·법관·중앙선거관리위원회 위원·감사원장·감사위원 기타 법률이 정한 공무원이 그 직무집행에 있어서 헌법이나 법률을 위배한 때에는 국회는 탄핵의 소추를 의결할 수 있다. 국민의 모든 자유와 권리는 국가안전보장·질서유지 또는 공공복리를 위하여 필요한 경우에 한하여 법률로써 제한할 수 있으며, 제한하는 경우에도 자유와 권리의 본질적인 내용을 침해할 수 없다.
두번째 문단이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;세번째 문단이다.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/%EC%98%88%EC%88%A0%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%98-%ED%94%BC</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/%EC%98%88%EC%88%A0%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%98-%ED%94%BC</guid>
                
                <category>life</category>
                
                <category>thoughts</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>