<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Das Kopfkinooo</title>
        <description></description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:13:21 +0100</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 02:13:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.0.1</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>Graphic Designer On The Road</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer is a professional within the graphic design and graphic arts industry who assembles together images, typography, or motion graphics to create a piece of design. A graphic designer creates the graphics primarily for published, printed or electronic media, such as brochures (sometimes) and advertising. They are also sometimes responsible for typesetting, illustration, user interfaces, web design, or take a teaching position. A core responsibility of the designer’s job is to present information in a way that is both accessible and memorable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A degree or certificate from an accredited trade school is usually considered essential for a graphic design position. After a career history has been established, though, the graphic designer’s experience and number of years in the business are considered the primary qualifications. A portfolio, which is the primary method for demonstrating these qualifications, is usually required to be shown at job interviews, and is constantly developed throughout a designer’s career. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Graphic_designer&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ice molecules can exhibit up to sixteen different phases &lt;em&gt;(packing geometries)&lt;/em&gt; that depend on temperature and pressure. When water is cooled rapidly (quenching), up to three different types of amorphous ice can form depending on the history of its pressure and temperature. When cooled slowly correlated proton tunneling occurs below 20 K giving rise to macroscopic quantum phenomena. Virtually all the ice on Earth’s surface and in its atmosphere is of a hexagonal crystalline structure denoted as ice Ih (spoken as “ice one h”) with minute traces of cubic ice denoted as ice Ic. The most common phase transition to ice Ih occurs when liquid water is cooled below 0°C (273.15K, 32°F) at standard atmospheric pressure. It may also be deposited directly by water vapor, as happens in the formation of frost. The transition from ice to water is melting and from ice directly to water vapor is sublimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;characteristics&quot;&gt;Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a naturally-occurring crystalline inorganic solid with an ordered structure, ice is considered a mineral.[citation needed] It possesses a regular crystalline structure based on the molecule of water, which consists of a single oxygen atom covalently bonded to two hydrogen atoms, or H-O-H. However, many of the physical properties of water and ice are controlled by the formation of hydrogen bonds between adjacent oxygen and hydrogen atoms; while it is a weak bond, it is nonetheless critical in controlling the structure of both water and ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ice contains no future , just the past, sealed away. As if they’re alive, everything in the world is sealed up inside, clear and distinct. Ice can preserve all kinds of things that way- cleanly, clearly. That’s the essence of ice, the role it plays.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Haruki Murakami&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unusual property of ice frozen at atmospheric pressure is that the solid is approximately 8.3% less dense than liquid water. The density of ice is 0.9167 g/cm3 at 0 °C,[4] whereas water has a density of 0.9998 g/cm³ at the same temperature. Liquid water is densest, essentially 1.00 g/cm³, at 4 °C and becomes less dense as the water molecules begin to form the hexagonal crystals[5] of ice as the freezing point is reached. This is due to hydrogen bonding dominating the intermolecular forces, which results in a packing of molecules less compact in the solid. Density of ice increases slightly with decreasing temperature and has a value of 0.9340 g/cm³ at −180 °C (93 K).[6]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When water freezes, it increases in volume (about 9% for freshwater).[7] The effect of expansion during freezing can be dramatic, and ice expansion is a basic cause of freeze-thaw weathering of rock in nature and damage to building foundations and roadways from frost heaving. It is also a common cause of the flooding of houses when water pipes burst due to the pressure of expanding water when it freezes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of this process is that ice &lt;em&gt;(in its most common form)&lt;/em&gt; floats on liquid water, which is an important feature in Earth’s biosphere. It has been argued that without this property, natural bodies of water would freeze, in some cases permanently, from the bottom up,[8] resulting in a loss of bottom-dependent animal and plant life in fresh and sea water. Sufficiently thin ice sheets allow light to pass through while protecting the underside from short-term weather extremes such as wind chill. This creates a sheltered environment for bacterial and algal colonies. When sea water freezes, the ice is riddled with brine-filled channels which sustain sympagic organisms such as bacteria, algae, copepods and annelids, which in turn provide food for animals such as krill and specialised fish like the bald notothen, fed upon in turn by larger animals such as emperor penguins and minke whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ice melts, it absorbs as much energy as it would take to heat an equivalent mass of water by 80 °C. During the melting process, the temperature remains constant at 0 °C. While melting, any energy added breaks the hydrogen bonds between ice (water) molecules. Energy becomes available to increase the thermal energy (temperature) only after enough hydrogen bonds are broken that the ice can be considered liquid water. The amount of energy consumed in breaking hydrogen bonds in the transition from ice to water is known as the heat of fusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with water, ice absorbs light at the red end of the spectrum preferentially as the result of an overtone of an oxygen-hydrogen (O-H) bond stretch. Compared with water, this absorption is shifted toward slightly lower energies. Thus, ice appears blue, with a slightly greener tint than for liquid water. Since absorption is cumulative, the color effect intensifies with increasing thickness or if internal reflections cause the light to take a longer path through the ice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>The Advantages &amp; Disadvantages of Working from Home</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A work at home parent is an entrepreneur who works from home and integrates parenting into his or her business activities. They are sometimes referred to as a WAHM &lt;em&gt;(work at home mom)&lt;/em&gt; or a WAHD &lt;em&gt;(work at home dad)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneurs choose to run businesses from home for a variety of reasons, including lower business expenses, personal health limitations, eliminating commuting, or in order to have a more flexible schedule. This flexibility can give an entrepreneur more options when planning tasks, business and non-business, including parenting duties. While some home-based entrepreneurs opt for childcare outside the home,[1] others integrate child rearing into their work day and workspace. The latter are considered work-at-home parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many WAHPs start home-based businesses in order to care for their children while still creating income. The desire to care for one’s own children, the incompatibility of a 9-to-5 work day with school hours or sick days, and the expense of childcare prompt many parents to change or leave their jobs in the workforce to be available to their children. Many WAHPs build a business schedule that can be integrated with their parenting duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;concept&quot;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fusion Festival combines all styles of the underground electronic music scene and various other styles, sometimes depending on the attendees who choose to play their own music. It is described as a space people go to free their minds from their everyday lives, jobs, studies and other responsibilities. It is the result of the search for an alternative through music, to the system “people are forced to live in”. People go to the Fusion to experience a different way of socializing and living, where experiencing one another freely, sharing love for music and art connects different scenes and minds. It is a clothing-optional event. Art installations include performance arts, static artworks, sculptures, art cars and various other forms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusion Festival began in 1997 near the city of Lärz in north-eastern Germany, about 160 km from Berlin and 230 km from Hamburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;festival-site&quot;&gt;Festival Site&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location is on the original grass-covered grounds of a disused military airfield (at 53°20′48.11″N 12°44′23.25″E for the 234-hectare area central field) about 4.5 km (2.25 miles) due north of the modern Rechlin-Lärz Airfield facility. The site was first acquired by the German Empire in 1916 as an aviation research and training ground, opening the facility for use by the Luftstreitkräfte in August 1918. After the establishment of the Luftwaffe in 1935, the field served as the Erprobungsstelle Rechlin central military aircraft test facility of the Third Reich through early 1945, and it was captured by the Soviet Red Army on May 2, 1945, for use by the VVS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are grass-covered concrete hangars (actual bunkers) from that time that were used for Soviet fighter aircraft (hence the Cyrillic transliteration of the festival name and various stages, as many Cyrillic inscriptions were still present on the site). The airfield was reopened for civilian use in 1994 and sold to the Müritz Airpark Group in 2010. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fusion_Festival&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>